Finding Aid for the Farley Edward Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Farley Edward Papers
Undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0134
8.25 linear_feet
- Lectures (Courses) DePauw University (1950’s)
  - - Lectures, Chinese Religions (Box 1)
  - - Lectures, Hinduism (Box 1)
  - - Feminist Theology - Writings and Lectures (Box 1)
  - - Reading Theological Texts (Box 1)
  - - Tradition (Course) (Box 1)
  - - Theological Bibliography (Box 1)
  - - Essence of Christianity (Box 1)
  - - Contemporary Theology: Lectures (Box 1)
  - - History of Philosophy, Ancient (Box 1)
  - - Contemporary Philosophy (Box 1)
  - - Christian Thought (Box 1)
  - - Introduction to Christian Thought (Box 1)
  - - Introduction to Christian Theology (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology: Prologue (?) (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology I, (1967) (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology: Ccourse, (1971-72, 1973, 74) (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology: God (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology: Salvation, Christology (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Theological Method, Introduction to Theology (Box 1)
  - - Introduction, Christian Theology II (Christology, God) (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology: Lectures - Theological Method, (1981) (Box 1)
  - - Introduction. Systematic Theology, (1984-85) (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Introduction. Christian Thought, Theology II (Box 1)
  - - Theology, Method: Truth, (1981-82) (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Theological Anthropology (Religious Consciousness, Imago) (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Ecclesiology (Box 1)
  - - Systematic Theology - Presentations, (1971-72) (Box 1)
  - - Introduction: Systematic Theology (Syllabi) (Box 1)
  - - Systematics: Knowledge of God (Box 1)
  - - Systematics: Theology of God (Box 1)
  - - Systematics: Part II (B) Salvation (Box 1)
  - - Systematics: Part II (A) Sin (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Appresence (?)of God (Box 1)
  - - Lectures: Divine Activity: World Process (Providence & Creation) (Box 1)
  - - The Minister as Theologian (Box 1)
  - - God & Evil: Theodicy Seminar (Box 1)
- Graduate Department of Religion Files and Divinity School Committee Files
  - - CTE: Materials (Retreats I, II/Faculty Interview), (1977-78) (Box 2)
  - - C.E.T., (1978-79) (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Committee (Box 2)
  - - A & P Committt:t: (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Documents (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Materials, Misc. (Box 2)
  - - (C.T.E.) Reports, (March/ April 1979, February 1980) (Box 2)
  - - Faculty Minutes, (Fall 1980) (Box 2)
  - - P & P (Personnel & Policy) Committee, (1989-90) (Box 2)
  - - P & P (Personnel & Policy), (1989-90) (Box 2)
  - - P & P (Personnel & Po licy) Minutes, (1986 ... ) (Box 2)
  - - P & P (Personnel & Policy) Committee, (1978-79) (Box 2)
  - - Catalogues and Brouchure (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Report, (February 1981) (Box 2)
  - - Curriculum Plan II, (January 1980) (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Faculty Communication (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Course Descriptions (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Communications To and From Others, (1980-81) (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Curriculum Schemes (Box 2)
  - - C.T.E. Committee, (1980-1981) (Box 2)
  - - GDR. FAC. Roti (May 1991) (Grad. Dept. of Rei.) (Box 2)
  - - GDR Conference (Nov 1991) (Grad. Dept of Rei.) (Box 2)
  - - GDR Reorganization Proposals (Box 2)
  - - LRP, Documents TWO (Long Range Planning) (Box 2)
  - - GDR. Faculty Responses (Box 2)
  - - GDR: Long Range Planning Committee (Box 2)
  - - GDR: Long Range. Studies & Documents (Box 2)
  - - Materials: Grad. Theel. (Box 2)
- Committee Documents Material and Graduate Departmemt of Religion Files
  - - Applications - Grants, (1969-1987) (Box 3)
  - - Research Council Applictions (Box 3)
  - - Leaves & Sabbatical Schedules (Box 3)
  - - Lilly: 1988-89 Leave (Box 3)
  - - Ph.D. Program in Theology (Box 3)
  - - Torah (Box 3)
  - - Grad. Students: List (Box 3)
  - - Dissertation Form, Rules (Box 3)
  - - Tenure, Promotion. Rules, Procedure of Schools (Box 3)
  - - Ph.D. Exams (Box 3)
  - - Student Aid: MA PhD (Box 3)
  - - GDR: Policy, Admissions (Box 3)
  - - M.A.Degree (Box 3)
  - - GDR: Area Studies (Box 3)
  - - Theology PhD’s, Progress, Programs (Box 3)
  - - GDR Minutes (Box 3)
  - - Quali fying Exams: Theology (Box 3)
  - - Current Jobs. Correspondence. Grad Students (Box 3)
  - - Descriptions/Guidelines Qualyfying Exams (Box 3)
  - - Theology Area (Box 3)
  - - Admissions; Correspondence (Box 3)
  - - YDS: Statistics, Students (Box 3)
  - - YDS: General lnfromation/ Issues (Box 3)
  - - Racism Document, etc. (Box 3)
  - - VDS Budget, (1990. .. ) (Box 3)
  - - New Doctor’s Degree (Box 3)
  - - Steering Committee, (1985) (Box 3)
  - - Special Programs (VDS) (Box 3)
  - - Divinity Library (Box 3)
  - - VDS, Promotional Materials (Box 3)
  - - Divinity School: Administration. Response Structures (Box 3)
  - - Tenure/Promotion Guidelines (Box 3)
  - - VDS, & Joint Degree Programs (Box 3)
  - - Curriculum: M.Div (Information, review) (Box 3)
  - - Grades - VDS (Box 3)
  - - Faculty Minutes, (1986- 1994) (Box 3)
  - - Vand. Self-Study/ATS Review (Box 3)
  - - GDR/Faculty Revision(?) (Box 3)
  - - Lilly Committee (Box 3)
  - - Long Range Planning (Box 3)
  - - Program Focus (Box 3)
  - - KMS Institute (Box 3)
  - - VDS: Long-Term Plan (Box 3)
  - - P.P. Constitution (Box 3)
  - - Master of Theological Studies (Box 3)
  - - Tenure, Promotion (Box 3)
  - - Master of Sacred Music (Box 3)
  - - PhD Admission Records (Older Files) (Box 3)
- Conferences/Constultations, Research Notes
  - - Hastings Center, (Conference, May 1997) (Box 4)
  - - Graduate Theological Education Conference, (June 1992) (Box 4)
  - - Conference, “Practical Theology”, (Chicago, 1983) (Box 4)
  - - VDS Conference on Theological Education, (Fall, 1979) (Box 4)
  - - Auburn Conference, Graduate Theological Education (Box 4)
  - - Theology & Religious Studies (Box 4)
  - - Theological Ed.: Miscell. (Box 4)
  - - Papers: Vanderbilt Conference, (Fall, 1979) (Box 4)
  - - Yale Conferences- Arts & (?) (Box 4)
  - - Literature & Theological Education Conference (Box 4)
  - - Auburn: Grad. Theol. Ed. Studies (Box 4)
  - - Auburn Studies (Theol. Ed.) (Box 4)
  - - Wheeler(?) Center for Theol. Ed. (Auburn) (Box 4)
  - - Piety & Intellect, (Indianapolis, Oct. 20 (1992) (Box 4)
  - - Lilly Conference. Theol. Ed. & Forms, (May, 1995) (Box 4)
  - - Wheeler-Kelsey Report (Lilly Grants, - Theol. Ed.) (Box 4)
  - - Papers: Santa Barbara (Box 4)
  - - Episcopal Curriculum & Loyola, “Education for Ministry” (Box 4)
  - - Popular Religion & Ed. (Box 4)
  - - Congregational (?) Theo. Ed. - Lilly (Box 4)
  - - Lilly Grant: Budget, Expenses (Box 4)
  - - Lilly Foundation: Older Corresondences (Box 4)
  - - A TS: Basic Issues Forums (Box 4)
  - - Divinity Schools- Universities (Box 4)
  - - Notes & Data: Grad. Theol. Ed. (Box 4)
  - - Theology. Education. USA, History of (Box 4)
  - - Ph.D. Program: Formulations (Box 4)
  - - Reading Notes: Current Theo. Ed. (Box 4)
  - - Philosophers (Box 4)
  - - Religious Studies (Box 4)
  - - Against Fields (Box 4)
  - - History of Universitites, Higher Ed. (Box 4)
  - - Readings: Disciplines, Sciences, Specialism (Box 4)
  - - Faculty Scholarship- Lilly (Theological Schools) (Box 4)
  - - A TS/Lilly Conferences on Theologia (Box 4)
  - - Theological Education: Correspondences (Box 4)
  - - The Enlightenment & Critical Principle (Notes) (Box 4)
  - - Various Theological Disciplines (Ethics, etc.) (Box 4)
  - - History, Theological Education (Secondary) (Box 4)
  - - Theology- Encyclopedia: Bibliography (Box 4)
  - - History of: Encyclopedia: Secondary (Box 4)
  - - Formulations: Theological Education (Box 4)
  - - Theo. Ed. - USA & Europe (?) Primary (Box 4)
  - - Miller (Box 4)
  - - Xeroxed Articles (Box 4)
  - - Xeroxed Table of Contents (Box 4)
  - - 18th C. Encyclopedia (Prot.) (Box 4)
  - - Pre 18th C.: Catholic (Box 4)
  - - 19th C. Protestant. Encyclopedia (Box 4)
  - - Bibliography. Catholic, All Periods (Box 4)
  - - Post-Medieval Catholic Encyclopedia (Box 4)
  - - 20th Century Encyclopedia (Box 4)
  - - Theological. Encyclopedia. Charts (Box 4)
  - - Church History (Box 4)
  - - Practical Theology: Historical (Box 4)
  - - Practical Theology. Formulations (Box 4)
  - - Practical Theology: Contemporary (Box 4)
  - - Homiletics (Box 4)
  - - Doctor of Theology, Ministry (Box 4)
  - - Readings: Christian Education (Box 4)
- Early Manuscripts for Publication
  - - AAR Review - Theology Sections (Box 5)
  - - St. John’s Project. Gospel, Congregational Reform (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: Good & Evil (I st Proof), (Aug 13, 1990) (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: (?) Proof, (Plimpton Press, May 27, ’ 960) (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: Requiem for a Lost Piety (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: (?) Proof (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: (?)Proof, (Fortress Press, 1982) (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: Madness & Evil: An Essay on the Human Problem (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: Requiem for a Lost Piety: The Contemporary Search for the Christian Life (Box 5)
  - - Manuscript: The Most High: A Study of the Doctrine of Transcendence of God in Contemporary Phi losophical Theology (Box 5)